A Guide to the Institute of International Education records, Alumni and Historical Files, RG 1 FA1289
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Historical Files, 3
  - American Civil Liberties Union 1948 (Reel 14, Side 2, Index 3), Reel 14, Side 2, Index 3 (Reel 14)
  - Arizona State College Request for German Scientists in Medical Research Lab 1949 (Reel 20, Side 2, Index 3), Reel 20, Side 2, Index 3 (Reel 20)
  - Association of American Colleges for Teacher Education 1949 (Reel 20, Side 2, Index 4), Reel 20, Side 2, Index 4 (Reel 20)
  - Africa General 1949-1950 (Reel 17, Side 1, Index 10), Reel 17, Side 1, Index 10 (Reel 17)
  - Africa General 1950 (Reel 19, Side 1, Index 14), Reel 19, Side 1, Index 14 (Reel 19)
  - American Association of Colleges for Teacher Education German Student Teacher Orientation 1950 (Reel 20, Side 2, Index 5), Reel 20, Side 2, Index 5 (Reel 20)
  - Association of American Colleges for Teacher Education Evaluation Meeting 1949 (Reel 20, Side 2, Index 12), Reel 20, Side 2, Index 12 (Reel 20)
  - Special Projects American Council for Voluntary Agencies Proposals for Japanese Counselors Project 1952-1954 (Reel 25, Side 1, Index 25), Reel 25, Side 1, Index 25 (Reel 25)
  - American Scandinavian Foundation Correspondence 1953 (Reel 30, Side 1, Index 9), Reel 30, Side 1, Index 9 (Reel 30)
  - American Scandinavian Foundation Correspondence 1956-1957 1956 (Reel 33, Side 2, Index 9), Reel 33, Side 2, Index 9 (Reel 33)
  - Australia Selection Committee Department of State General Correspondence 1957-1958 1956-1957 (Reel 30, Side 1, Index 39), Reel 30, Side 1, Index 39 (Reel 30)
  - American Council on Education 1921-1923 IIE Correspondence 1919 (Reel 2, Side 2, Index 18), Reel 2, Side 2, Index 18 (Reel 2)
  - American Council on Education 1935 (Reel 11, Side 1, Index 37), Reel 11, Side 1, Index 37 (Reel 11)
  - American Council on Education 1936 (Reel 5, Side 1, Index 23), Reel 5, Side 1, Index 23 (Reel 5)
  - American Council on Education 1937 (Reel 7, Side 2, Index 2), Reel 7, Side 2, Index 2 (Reel 7)
  - American Council on Education 1938 (Reel 7, Side 2, Index 39), Reel 7, Side 2, Index 39 (Reel 7)
  - American Council on Education 1940 (Reel 10, Side 1, Index 22), Reel 10, Side 1, Index 22 (Reel 10)
  - American Council on Education 1942 (Reel 12, Side 1, Index 19), Reel 12, Side 1, Index 19 (Reel 12)
  - American Council on Education 1943 (Reel 13, Side 1, Index 50), Reel 13, Side 1, Index 50 (Reel 13)
  - American Council on Education 1944 (Reel 13, Side 2, Index 11), Reel 13, Side 2, Index 11 (Reel 13)
  - American Council on education 1945 (Reel 14, Side 1, Index 29), Reel 14, Side 1, Index 29 (Reel 14)
  - American Council on Eudcation Meeting of Committtee on Financial Aid Dec 2 1946 1946 (Reel 15, Side 1, Index 3), Reel 15, Side 1, Index 3 (Reel 15)
  - American Council on Education 1947 (Reel 15, Side 2, Index 14), Reel 15, Side 2, Index 14 (Reel 15)
  - American Council on Education Suggestions to Spoksers for exchange of Persons Program with Occupied Areas 1950 (Reel 19, Side 2, Index 14), Reel 19, Side 2, Index 14 (Reel 19)
  - American Council on Education Relations with IIE on Proposed Coordination of International Exchange 1951 (Reel 28, Side 2, Index 17), Reel 28, Side 2, Index 17 (Reel 28)
  - American Field Service Fellowships General Correspondence 1919-25 (Reel 2, Side 2, Index 10), Reel 2, Side 2, Index 10 (Reel 2)
  - American Field Service Fellowships Trustee Minutes 1919-1920 (Reel 2, Side 1, Index 12), Reel 2, Side 1, Index 12 (Reel 2)
  - American Field Service Fellowships For French Universities Pledges Complete 1919-1920 (Reel 3, Side 1, Index 28), Reel 3, Side 1, Index 28 (Reel 3)
  - American Field Service 1919-1923 (Reel 3, Side 1, Index 18), Reel 3, Side 1, Index 18 (Reel 3)
  - American Field Service Fellowships 1919-1924 (Reel 3, Side 1, Index 17), Reel 3, Side 1, Index 17 (Reel 3)
  - Clippings 1919-1922 Paul D. Cravath American Field Service Fellowships 1919-1924 (Reel 3, Side 1, Index 21), Reel 3, Side 1, Index 21 (Reel 3)
  - American Field Service American University Union etc. 1919-1924 (Reel 3, Side 1, Index 26), Reel 3, Side 1, Index 26 (Reel 3)
  - Society for American Fellowships in French Universities Meeting of Trustees - Minutes etc. 1919-1924 (Reel 3, Side 1, Index 32), Reel 3, Side 1, Index 32 (Reel 3)
  - American Field Service Fellowships 1919-1925 (Reel 2, Side 2, Index 9), Reel 2, Side 2, Index 9 (Reel 2)
  - American Field Service Fellowships General Correspondence 1919-1925 (Reel 2, Side 2, Index 10), Reel 2, Side 2, Index 10 (Reel 2)
  - American Field Service Fellowships for French Universities Receips and Duplicates 1920 (Reel 3, Side 2, Index 3), Reel 3, Side 2, Index 3 (Reel 3)
  - Refereees 1920-1923 (Reel 3, Side 1, Index 23), Reel 3, Side 1, Index 23 (Reel 3)
  - American Field Service Fellowships for French Universities Financial 1920-1924 (Reel 3, Side 2, Index 2), Reel 3, Side 2, Index 2 (Reel 3)
  - American Field Service Fellowships For French Universities Subsription Pledges 1921 (Reel 3, Side 2, Index 33), Reel 3, Side 2, Index 33 (Reel 3)
  - American Field Service Fellowships for French Universities Financial - Charles A. Fulcher Assistant Treasurer 1921-1924 (Reel 3, Side 1, Index 27), Reel 3, Side 1, Index 27 (Reel 3)
  - Society of American Field Service Fellowships- Trustees Reorganization of Board 1923 (Reel 3, Side 1, Index 22), Reel 3, Side 1, Index 22 (Reel 3)
  - George Clemenceau Donation to American Field Service Fellowships 1923 (Reel 3, Side 1, Index 31), Reel 3, Side 1, Index 31 (Reel 3)
  - American Field Service Fellowships Personality Ratings of Applicants 1923-1924 (Reel 3, Side 1, Index 29), Reel 3, Side 1, Index 29 (Reel 3)
  - American Field Service Fellowships for French Universities Financial Campaign 1923-1924 (Reel 3, Side 2, Index 1), Reel 3, Side 2, Index 1 (Reel 3)
  - American Field Service Fellowships Paul D. Cravath Esq. (Inst. Takes over American Field Service) 1924 (Reel 3, Side 1, Index 16), Reel 3, Side 1, Index 16 (Reel 3)
  - C.A. Coffin Esq. Society of American Field Service Fellowships 1924 (Reel 3, Side 1, Index 20), Reel 3, Side 1, Index 20 (Reel 3)
  - American Field Service Fellowships For French Universities Executive Committee 1924-1925 (Reel 3, Side 1, Index 25), Reel 3, Side 1, Index 25 (Reel 3)
  - American Field Service Fellowships Proceedings 1924-1925 (Reel 2, Side 2, Index 13), Reel 2, Side 2, Index 13 (Reel 2)
  - American Field Service Fellowships Survey on International Fellowships A-Z 1929 (Reel 3, Side 1, Index 4), Reel 3, Side 1, Index 4 (Reel 3)
  - American Field Serivce in France (AFSF) General 1933 (Reel 4, Side 1, Index 32), Reel 4, Side 1, Index 32 (Reel 4)
  - American Field Service Fellowships Successful 1932-1933 1935 (Reel 10, Side 2, Index 50), Reel 10, Side 2, Index 50 (Reel 10)
  - American Field Service Fellowships General A-Z 1935 (Reel 11, Side 1, Index 49), Reel 11, Side 1, Index 49 (Reel 11)
  - American Field Service Fellowships 1937-1938 (Reel 2, Side 2, Index 14), Reel 2, Side 2, Index 14 (Reel 2)
  - American Field Service Fellowships General 1940 (Reel 10, Side 1, Index 25), Reel 10, Side 1, Index 25 (Reel 10)
  - American Field Service Fellowships 1942 (Reel 12, Side 2, Index 6), Reel 12, Side 2, Index 6 (Reel 12)
  - American Field Service Fellowships RE Field Service Directory 1942 (Reel 12, Side 2, Index 4), Reel 12, Side 2, Index 4 (Reel 12)
  - American Field Service Fellowships Field Service Directory 1942 (Reel 12, Side 2, Index 5), Reel 12, Side 2, Index 5 (Reel 12)
  - American Field Serivice Fellowships For French Universities, Inc. 1949-1950 (Reel 17, Side 1, Index 7), Reel 17, Side 1, Index 7 (Reel 17)
  - American Field Service Fellowships 1950-1951 (Reel 20, Side 1, Index 5), Reel 20, Side 1, Index 5 (Reel 20)
  - American University Union Board of Trustees Minutes 1916-1919 (Reel 1, Side 2, Index 21), Reel 1, Side 2, Index 21 (Reel 1)
  - American University Union in Europe Alumni Council of Amherst College Correspondence 1917 (Reel 1, Side 1, Index 1), Reel 1, Side 1, Index 1 (Reel 1)
  - American Universitey Union Honorary Members Contribution of the Union 1917 (Reel 1, Side 1, Index 20), Reel 1, Side 1, Index 20 (Reel 1)
  - American University Union Major College Members Fraternities Minutes 1917 (Reel 1, Side 2, Index 1), Reel 1, Side 2, Index 1 (Reel 1)
  - American University Uniion Alphabetical College List for Membership Application 1917 (Reel 1, Side 2, Index 2), Reel 1, Side 2, Index 2 (Reel 1)
  - American University Union Subscription to Publications 1917 (Reel 1, Side 2, Index 3), Reel 1, Side 2, Index 3 (Reel 1)
  - American University Union Appointments in Paris, London Board of Trustee Meetings, Conferences, Contributions 1917-1918 (Reel 1, Side 1, Index 2), Reel 1, Side 1, Index 2 (Reel 1)
  - American University Union Election of Trustees, La Maison des Etudiants, Patrons, Student and Job Applications 1917-1918 (Reel 1, Side 1, Index 3), Reel 1, Side 1, Index 3 (Reel 1)
  - American University Union Pamphlet, Membership, Correspondence 1917-1918 (Reel 1, Side 1, Index 5), Reel 1, Side 1, Index 5 (Reel 1)
  - American University Union Yale, Vermont War Service Records Red Cross Shipments via War Relief Clearing House 1917-1918 (Reel 1, Side 1, Index 7), Reel 1, Side 1, Index 7 (Reel 1)
  - American University Union Britain 1917-1919 (Reel 1, Side 1, Index 4), Reel 1, Side 1, Index 4 (Reel 1)
  - American University Union Italy Education and Care of War Prisoners, London Report, Fund Raising, Correspondence 1917-1919 (Reel 1, Side 1, Index 9), Reel 1, Side 1, Index 9 (Reel 1)
  - American University Union Trustees Reorganization Plan, General Correspondence, France War Relief Work 1917-1919 (Reel 1, Side 1, Index 13), Reel 1, Side 1, Index 13 (Reel 1)
  - American University Union University Club 1917-1919 (Reel 1, Side 2, Index 10), Reel 1, Side 2, Index 10 (Reel 1)
  - American University Union Opening of Paris Headquarters, Sorbonne Meeting Reports of Executive Committee 1918 (Reel 1, Side 1, Index 6), Reel 1, Side 1, Index 6 (Reel 1)
  - American University Union Executive Committee Report, Correspondence Fund Raising, Paris Yale Bureau 1918 (Reel 1, Side 1, Index 10), Reel 1, Side 1, Index 10 (Reel 1)
  - American University Union Executive Committee Reports 1918 (Reel 1, Side 2, Index 4), Reel 1, Side 2, Index 4 (Reel 1)
  - American University Union Finances - Budget and Reports Henry B. Thompson Treasurer 1918 (Reel 1, Side 2, Index 5), Reel 1, Side 2, Index 5 (Reel 1)
  - American University Union W.T. Brewter 1918 (Reel 1, Side 2, Index 6), Reel 1, Side 2, Index 6 (Reel 1)
  - American University Union F.D. Fackethal 1918 (Reel 1, Side 2, Index 7), Reel 1, Side 2, Index 7 (Reel 1)
  - American University Union John H. Finley 1918 (Reel 1, Side 2, Index 8), Reel 1, Side 2, Index 8 (Reel 1)
  - American University Union France Rexford G. Tugwell General Correspondence 1918 (Reel 1, Side 2, Index 9), Reel 1, Side 2, Index 9 (Reel 1)
  - American University Union Newspaper Articles, Clippings, Press Releases 1918 (Reel 1, Side 2, Index 11), Reel 1, Side 2, Index 11 (Reel 1)
  - American University Union Subscriptions and Appeals 1918 (Reel 1, Side 2, Index 13), Reel 1, Side 2, Index 13 (Reel 1)
  - American University Union Fraternities 1918 (Reel 1, Side 2, Index 14), Reel 1, Side 2, Index 14 (Reel 1)
  - American University Union All College Rally 1918 (Reel 1, Side 2, Index 15), Reel 1, Side 2, Index 15 (Reel 1)
  - American University Union American Council on Education- Committee on International Educational Relations 1918 (Reel 1, Side 2, Index 16), Reel 1, Side 2, Index 16 (Reel 1)
  - American University Union Trustee Resolutions Copies of NY Vote Sevres Fellowships for Women 1918-1919 (Reel 1, Side 1, Index 8), Reel 1, Side 1, Index 8 (Reel 1)
  - American University Union Pamphlet, Library War Service Correspondence, Expenses 1918-1919 (Reel 1, Side 1, Index 11), Reel 1, Side 1, Index 11 (Reel 1)
  - American University Union Membership Applications, Annual Payment, Paris War Projects, General Correspondence 1918-1919 (Reel 1, Side 1, Index 12), Reel 1, Side 1, Index 12 (Reel 1)
  - American University Union Salary List, Contributions, General Correspondence, International Federation of University Women - Constitution 1918-1919 (Reel 1, Side 1, Index 15), Reel 1, Side 1, Index 15 (Reel 1)
  - American University Union American Council on Education - Minutes 1918-1919 (Reel 1, Side 2, Index 24), Reel 1, Side 2, Index 24 (Reel 1)
  - American University Union Subscriptions to Publications 1918-1919 (Reel 1, Side 2, Index 25), Reel 1, Side 2, Index 25 (Reel 1)
  - American University Union 1918-1919 (Reel 7, Side 1, Index 22), Reel 7, Side 1, Index 22 (Reel 7)
  - American University Union Paris Yale Bureau, Contributions, A.U.U. For College Women Plan 1919 (Reel 1, Side 1, Index 16), Reel 1, Side 1, Index 16 (Reel 1)
  - American University Union London, IIE Announcement Proceedings of Committee of Vice-Chancellors and Principals 1919 (Reel 1, Side 1, Index 17), Reel 1, Side 1, Index 17 (Reel 1)
  - American University Union College Members and Those Declining Meeting of Founders of Maison des Estudiants, Speech of Professor Nettleton 1919 (Reel 1, Side 1, Index 18), Reel 1, Side 1, Index 18 (Reel 1)
  - American University Union Circular Letters, Miscellaneous 1919 (Reel 1, Side 2, Index 12), Reel 1, Side 2, Index 12 (Reel 1)
  - American University Union Prof. Woods - Personal 1919 (Reel 1, Side 2, Index 17), Reel 1, Side 2, Index 17 (Reel 1)
  - American University Union J.W. Cunliffe 1919 (Reel 1, Side 2, Index 18), Reel 1, Side 2, Index 18 (Reel 1)
  - American University Union Dean Henry Yeomans 1919 (Reel 1, Side 2, Index 19), Reel 1, Side 2, Index 19 (Reel 1)
  - American University Union John H. Wigmore 1919 (Reel 1, Side 2, Index 20), Reel 1, Side 2, Index 20 (Reel 1)
  - American University Union Dinner Guests April 19, 1919 (Reel 1, Side 2, Index 22), Reel 1, Side 2, Index 22 (Reel 1)
  - American University Union Memoranda, Duplicate Copies, Minutes, Form Letters, etc. 1919 (Reel 1, Side 2, Index 26), Reel 1, Side 2, Index 26 (Reel 1)
  - American University Union Chinese Folder 1919 (Reel 1, Side 2, Index 27), Reel 1, Side 2, Index 27 (Reel 1)
  - American University Union Prof. Duggan 1919 (Reel 1, Side 2, Index 28), Reel 1, Side 2, Index 28 (Reel 1)
  - American University Union American Association of University Professors 1919 (Reel 1, Side 2, Index 23), Reel 1, Side 2, Index 23 (Reel 1)
  - American University Union General Correspondence 1919-1920 (Reel 1, Side 1, Index 19), Reel 1, Side 1, Index 19 (Reel 1)
  - American University Union Budget, Treaturer's Report Minutes, Trustee Meeting 1919-1922 (Reel 1, Side 2, Index 30), Reel 1, Side 2, Index 30 (Reel 1)
  - American University Union Correspondence Europe 1919-1924 (Reel 3, Side 1, Index 11), Reel 3, Side 1, Index 11 (Reel 3)
  - American University Union London Offices - Reports 1919, 1924-1926 (Reel 1, Side 2, Index 29), Reel 1, Side 2, Index 29 (Reel 1)
  - American University Union France - Annual Reports 1922-1924 (Reel 1, Side 2, Index 31), Reel 1, Side 2, Index 31 (Reel 1)
  - American University Union France and Britain - Reports 1923-1928 (Reel 1, Side 2, Index 32), Reel 1, Side 2, Index 32 (Reel 1)
  - American University Union Horatio S. Krans 1924 (Reel 3, Side 1, Index 19), Reel 3, Side 1, Index 19 (Reel 3)
  - American University Union Britain - Reports 1925-1927 (Reel 1, Side 2, Index 33), Reel 1, Side 2, Index 33 (Reel 1)
  - American University Union RE: Budget of Paris Office 1927 (Reel 18, Side 1, Index 18), Reel 18, Side 1, Index 18 (Reel 18)
  - American University Union Cite Universitaire 1928 (Reel 3, Side 1, Index 1), Reel 3, Side 1, Index 1 (Reel 3)
  - American University Union Britain 1929 (Reel 2, Side 1, Index 1), Reel 2, Side 1, Index 1 (Reel 2)
  - American University Union Correspondence Europe 1930 (Reel 3, Side 1, Index 12), Reel 3, Side 1, Index 12 (Reel 3)
  - American University Union Britain 1930 (Reel 3, Side 2, Index 29), Reel 3, Side 2, Index 29 (Reel 3)
  - American University Union Correspondence U.S. 1930 (Reel 3, Side 1, Index 13), Reel 3, Side 1, Index 13 (Reel 3)
  - American University Union in France - The American Cultural Influence in Europe 1931 (Reel 3, Side 2, Index 11), Reel 3, Side 2, Index 11 (Reel 3)
  - American University Union in U.S. 1931 (Reel 3, Side 2, Index 12), Reel 3, Side 2, Index 12 (Reel 3)
  - American University Union France 1931 (Reel 3, Side 2, Index 21), Reel 3, Side 2, Index 21 (Reel 3)
  - American University Union Britain 1932 (Reel 3, Side 2, Index 20), Reel 3, Side 2, Index 20 (Reel 3)
  - American University Union in U.S. 1932 (Reel 3, Side 2, Index 22), Reel 3, Side 2, Index 22 (Reel 3)
  - American University Union in Italy 1932 (Reel 3, Side 2, Index 28), Reel 3, Side 2, Index 28 (Reel 3)
  - American University Union Britain 1934 (Reel 4, Side 2, Index 32), Reel 4, Side 2, Index 32 (Reel 4)
  - American University Union in U.S. 1934 (Reel 4, Side 2, Index 30), Reel 4, Side 2, Index 30 (Reel 4)
  - American University Union in U.S. 1934 (Reel 4, Side 2, Index 31), Reel 4, Side 2, Index 31 (Reel 4)
  - American University Union France 1935 (Reel 10, Side 2, Index 18), Reel 10, Side 2, Index 18 (Reel 10)
  - American University Union Britain 1935 (Reel 10, Side 2, Index 17), Reel 10, Side 2, Index 17 (Reel 10)
  - American University Union in U.S. 1935 (Reel 10, Side 2, Index 19), Reel 10, Side 2, Index 19 (Reel 10)
  - American University Union Correspondence, Minutes, Annual Reports 1936 (Reel 2, Side 1, Index 2), Reel 2, Side 1, Index 2 (Reel 2)
  - American University Union Britain 1936 (Reel 2, Side 1, Index 3), Reel 2, Side 1, Index 3 (Reel 2)
  - American University Union Britain - Connley's Visit 1936 (Reel 2, Side 1, Index 4), Reel 2, Side 1, Index 4 (Reel 2)
  - American University Union France 1936 (Reel 2, Side 1, Index 5), Reel 2, Side 1, Index 5 (Reel 2)
  - American University Union France 1937 (Reel 7, Side 1, Index 27), Reel 7, Side 1, Index 27 (Reel 7)
  - American University Union Britain 1937 (Reel 7, Side 2, Index 3), Reel 7, Side 2, Index 3 (Reel 7)
  - American University Union U.S. - Committee on the A.U.U of The Institute of International Education 1937 (Reel 2, Side 1, Index 6), Reel 2, Side 1, Index 6 (Reel 2)
  - American University Union Correspondence 1938 (Reel 2, Side 1, Index 7), Reel 2, Side 1, Index 7 (Reel 2)
  - American University Union France 1938 (Reel 7, Side 1, Index 30), Reel 7, Side 1, Index 30 (Reel 7)
  - American University Union Britain 1938 (Reel 7, Side 2, Index 42), Reel 7, Side 2, Index 42 (Reel 7)
  - American University Union in the U.S. Minutes, Correspondence, etc. 1938 (Reel 7, Side 1, Index 20), Reel 7, Side 1, Index 20 (Reel 7)
  - American University Union Finances -1938 (Reel 7, Side 1, Index 8), Reel 7, Side 1, Index 8 (Reel 7)
  - American University Union France 1939 (Reel 9, Side 1, Index 6), Reel 9, Side 1, Index 6 (Reel 9)
  - American University Union England 1939 (Reel 10, Side 1, Index 5), Reel 10, Side 1, Index 5 (Reel 10)
  - American University Union U.S. 1939 (Reel 2, Side 1, Index 9), Reel 2, Side 1, Index 9 (Reel 2)
  - American University Union France 1940 (Reel 10, Side 1, Index 9), Reel 10, Side 1, Index 9 (Reel 10)
  - American University Union France - England 1940 (Reel 9, Side 1, Index 19), Reel 9, Side 1, Index 19 (Reel 9)
  - American University Union U.S. General Correspondence, Minutes Committee on the A.U.U of The Institute of International Education, Finances 1940-1941 (Reel 2, Side 1, Index 10), Reel 2, Side 1, Index 10 (Reel 2)
  - American University Union France - Horatio S. Krans in U.S. 1942 (Reel 12, Side 1, Index 20), Reel 12, Side 1, Index 20 (Reel 12)
  - American University Union England 1942 (Reel 12, Side 1, Index 21), Reel 12, Side 1, Index 21 (Reel 12)
  - American University Union Minutes 1942 (Reel 12, Side 1, Index 22), Reel 12, Side 1, Index 22 (Reel 12)
  - American University Union Meeting May 22, 1942 1942 (Reel 12, Side 1, Index 16), Reel 12, Side 1, Index 16 (Reel 12)
  - American University Union Britain 1943 (Reel 13, Side 1, Index 3), Reel 13, Side 1, Index 3 (Reel 13)
  - American University Union United States 1943 (Reel 13, Side 1, Index 51), Reel 13, Side 1, Index 51 (Reel 13)
  - American University Union France 1944 (Reel 13, Side 1, Index 58), Reel 13, Side 1, Index 58 (Reel 13)
  - American University Union Britain 1944 (Reel 13, Side 2, Index 10), Reel 13, Side 2, Index 10 (Reel 13)
  - American University Union United States 1944 (Reel 13, Side 1, Index 57), Reel 13, Side 1, Index 57 (Reel 13)
  - American University Union 1945 (Reel 14, Side 1, Index 21), Reel 14, Side 1, Index 21 (Reel 14)
  - American University Union Finances 1945 (Reel 14, Side 2, Index 1), Reel 14, Side 2, Index 1 (Reel 14)
  - American University Union France 1945 (Reel 14, Side 1, Index 20), Reel 14, Side 1, Index 20 (Reel 14)
  - American University Union Britain 1945 (Reel 14, Side 1, Index 30), Reel 14, Side 1, Index 30 (Reel 14)
  - American University Union France - Horatio S. Krans 1946 (Reel 15, Side 1, Index 5), Reel 15, Side 1, Index 5 (Reel 15)
  - American University Union Britain 1946 (Reel 15, Side 1, Index 2), Reel 15, Side 1, Index 2 (Reel 15)
  - American University Union United States 1946 (Reel 14, Side 2, Index 35), Reel 14, Side 2, Index 35 (Reel 14)
  - American University Union Publications 1946-1947 (Reel 2, Side 1, Index 11), Reel 2, Side 1, Index 11 (Reel 2)
  - American University Union 1947 (Reel 16, Side 1, Index 5), Reel 16, Side 1, Index 5 (Reel 16)
  - Austria Austro-American Student Exchange 1929 (Reel 3, Side 1, Index 6), Reel 3, Side 1, Index 6 (Reel 3)
  - Austria Correspondence RE: Dr. Paul L. Dengler 1929-1934, 1948-1948 (Reel 12, Side 1, Index 3), Reel 12, Side 1, Index 3 (Reel 12)
  - Austria Vienna Summer School 1930 (Reel 3, Side 2, Index 10), Reel 3, Side 2, Index 10 (Reel 3)
  - Austria Vienna Summer School 1931 (Reel 10, Side 2, Index 53), Reel 10, Side 2, Index 53 (Reel 10)
  - Austria Successful 1931-1932, 1935 (Reel 10, Side 2, Index 29), Reel 10, Side 2, Index 29 (Reel 10)
  - Austria-Vienna Summer School 1932 (Reel 4, Side 1, Index 13), Reel 4, Side 1, Index 13 (Reel 4)
  - Austria 1933 (Reel 4, Side 1, Index 25), Reel 4, Side 1, Index 25 (Reel 4)
  - Austria - Dr. Engler 1933 (Reel 4, Side 1, Index 33), Reel 4, Side 1, Index 33 (Reel 4)
  - Austria Vienna Fee Sent 1933 (Reel 4, Side 2, Index 13), Reel 4, Side 2, Index 13 (Reel 4)
  - Austria mondee Summer Session 1933 (Reel 4, Side 2, Index 14), Reel 4, Side 2, Index 14 (Reel 4)
  - Austria 1933 (Reel 4, Side 2, Index 15), Reel 4, Side 2, Index 15 (Reel 4)
  - Austria 1934 (Reel 11, Side 1, Index 11), Reel 11, Side 1, Index 11 (Reel 11)
  - Austria Junior Year Abroad General 1934 (Reel 11, Side 1, Index 12), Reel 11, Side 1, Index 12 (Reel 11)
  - Austria RE: Mondsee Institute 1934 (Reel 11, Side 1, Index 13), Reel 11, Side 1, Index 13 (Reel 11)
  - Austria Vienna Summer School 1934 (Reel 11, Side 1, Index 14), Reel 11, Side 1, Index 14 (Reel 11)
  - Special Projects Austria Dr. Walter Kotschnig 1934-1936 (Reel 8, Side 2, Index 3), Reel 8, Side 2, Index 3 (Reel 8)
  - Austria Dr. Paul L. Dengler Austrian Student Exchange 1934-1938 (Reel 12, Side 1, Index 1), Reel 12, Side 1, Index 1 (Reel 12)
  - Austria 1935 (Reel 5, Side 1, Index 10), Reel 5, Side 1, Index 10 (Reel 5)
  - Austria Special Projects Plan A 1935 (Reel 8, Side 1, Index 28), Reel 8, Side 1, Index 28 (Reel 8)
  - Austria Summer 1935 (Reel 11, Side 1, Index 39), Reel 11, Side 1, Index 39 (Reel 11)
  - Austria Summer 1936 (Reel 7, Side 2, Index 21), Reel 7, Side 2, Index 21 (Reel 7)
  - Austria Special Projects Plan B Dr. Karl Polanyi (Reel 8, Side 2, Index 16), Reel 8, Side 2, Index 16 (Reel 8)